#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/julie-b-79b74694 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing
Home Care
Registered Nurses

# Julie B.

Bachelor's degree at University of Central Florida United States

#### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Hospice & Palliative Medicine, Case Management, Oncology, and Patient Education. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing from University of Central Florida.

-Open to remote, virtual work only at this time.

### Experience

Kaiser Permanente Registered Nurse February 2015 - Present (5 years 6 months) United States

Hospice Case manager

American Mobile Healthcare Travel Nurse January 2014 - January 2015 (1 year 1 month) San Francisco Bay Area

Hospice contract with Kaiser Permanente

Community Hospice of Northeast Florida Triage nurse January 2012 - January 2014 (2 years 1 month) Jacksonville, Florida Area

Hospice

ST. VINCENT'S MEDICAL CENTER - CLAY COUNTY, INC Home Health Nurse January 2011 - January 2013 (2 years 1 month) Jacksonville, Florida Area Life Care Centers of America Rn/Supervisor October 2009 - January 2011 (1 year 4 months) Hilliard, FI

3-11 RN supervisor, charge nurse, and med nurse

## Education

University of Central Florida

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2011)

Florida State College at Jacksonville
Associate of Arts and Sciences (A.A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2005 - 2009)